Street & Smith Records
Street & Smith Records
- Scripts
  - The Shadow, American broadcast
    - no. 256 Gorilla Man, 21 Apr 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 30 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 257 The Dreams of Death, 28 Apr 1946; Coles, Stedman; 29 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 258 The White Witchman of Lawaiki, 5 May 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 29 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 259 The Bride Wore Black, 12 May 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 32 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 260 The Touch of Death, 19 May 1946; Coles, Stedman; 32 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 261 They Kill with a Silver Hatchet, 26 May 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 33 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 262 Death in a Minor Key, 2 Jun 1946; Wilson, Tom; 32 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 263 Vampires Prowl by Night, 8 Sep 1946; Fox, Gibson Scott; 30 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 264 The Killer on High Cliff Road, 15 Sep 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 33 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 265 Die, Lover - Die!, 22 Sep 1946; Fox, Gibson Scott; 31 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 266 Death Rides the Merry-Go-Round, 29 Sep 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 30 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 267 The Valley of Living Terror, 6 Oct 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; "Not aired due to [World] Series"; 30 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 268 The Valley of Living Terror, 13 Oct 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 26 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 269 Blood Money, 20 Oct 1946; Kane, Frank; 26 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 270 Cave of the Zombies, 27 Oct 1946; Morwood, William; 32 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 271 Murder for Blackmail, 3 Nov 1946; Coles, Stedman; 31 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 272 The Corpse without a Skin, 10 Nov 1946; Fox, Gibson Scott; 33 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 273 The Phantom of the Haunted Steeple, 17 Nov 1946; Wylie, Evan; 29 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 274 Gang Doctor, 24 Nov 1946; Kane, Frank; 29 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 275 Makeup for Murder, 1 Dec 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 30 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 276 The Devil Takes a Wife, 8 Dec 1946; Fox, Gibson Scott; 30 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 277 Murders on the Main Stem, 15 Dec 1946; Morwood, William; 31 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 278 The Fine Art of Murder, 22 Dec 1946; Smith, Joe Bates; 28 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 279 Shadow of Suspicion, 29 Dec 1946; Wylie, Evan; 32 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 280 The Werewolf of Hamilton Mansion, 5 Jan 1947; de Vry, Guy; 29 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 281 The Cat and the Killer, 12 Jan 1947; Reed, Lewis; 30 pp. (Box 363)
    - no. 282 A Game of Murder, 19 Jan 1947; Kane, Frank; 29 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 283 Death by Imagination, 26 Jan 1947; Morwood, William; 29 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 284 The Scent of Death, 2 Feb 1947; Kane, Frank; 31 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 285 Murder Marriage, 9 Feb 1947; Wylie, Evan; 26 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 286 Death Takes the Long Count, 16 Feb 1947; Kane, Frank; 30 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 287 The Witch of the Crescent Moon, 23 Feb 1947; Morwood, William; 30 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 288 Death Fans the Flame, 2 Mar 1947; Kane, Frank; 31 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 289 Mystery Ship, 9 Mar 1947; de Vry, Guy; 30 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 290 Murder by Appointment, 16 Mar 1947; Kane, Frank; 29 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 291 Death by Clockwork, 23 Mar 1947; Wylie, Evan; 31 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 292 Crime in a Minor Key, 30 Mar 1947; Kane, Frank; 28 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 293 The Great White Way to Death, 6 Apr 1947; Kane, Frank; 30 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 294 Death is the Keeper, 13 Apr 1947; Morwood, William; 33 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 295 Murder Express, 20 Apr 1947; Wylie, Evan; 32 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 296 Death Stakes a Handout, 27 Apr 1947; Kane, Frank; 31 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 297 Suicide League, 4 May 1947; de Vry, Guy; 32 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 298 The Shadow's Revenge, 11 May 1947; Kane, Frank; 33 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 299 Death Rides High, 18 May 1947; Kane, Frank; 30 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 300 Seance with Death, 25 May 1947; Kane, Frank; 32 pp. (Box 364)
    - 301, see bound volumes
    - no. 302 The Phantom of the Lighthouse, 7 Sep 1947; Morwood, William; 30 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 303 When the Grave is Open, 14 Sep 1947; Kane, Frank; 31 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 304 The Face, 21 Sep 1947; Ehrlich, Max; 30 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 305 Death Takes the Wheel, 28 Sep 1947; Kane, Frank; 31 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 306 The Curse of the Gypsies, 5 Oct 1947; Morwood, William; 31 pp. (Box 364)
    - no. 307 The Ruby of Karvahl, 19 Oct 1947; Barry, Peter; 36 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 308 Death Hunt, 26 Oct 1947; de Vry, Guy; 31 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 309 Death has Eight Arms, 2 Nov 1947; Morwood, William; 31 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 310 Dream of Death, 9 Nov 1947; Baldus, Frederic; 27 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 311 Doom and the Limping Man, 16 Nov 1947; Barry, Peter; 35 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 312 The Comic Strip Killer, 23 Nov 1947; Baumgartner, Herb; 30 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 313 Murder and the Medium, 30 Nov 1947; Barry, Peter; 32 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 314 Death Has Sharp Claws, 7 Dec 1947; Kane, Frank; 33 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 315 The Three Mad Sisters of Lonely Hollow, 14 Dec 1947; Baldus, Bud; 28 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 316 A Gift of Murder, 21 Dec 1947; Barry, Peter; 36 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 317 The Terrible Legend of Crownshield Castle, 28 Dec 1947; Baumgartner, Herb; 34 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 318 The Chill of Death, 4 Jan 1948; Vites, Louis; 30 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 319 Bones of the Dragon, 11 Jan 1948; Fox, Gibson Scott; 30 pp. (Box 365)
    - 320, see bound volumes
    - no. 321 The House That Death Built, 25 Jan 1948; Bester, Alfred; 32 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 322 One Dead and Two to Go, 1 Feb 1948; Kane, Frank; 34 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 323 The Thing in the Cage, 8 Feb 1948; Baumgartner, Herb; 29 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 324 The Terror at Wolf's Head Knoll, 15 Feb 1948; Barry, Peter; 33 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 325 The Nursery Rhyme Murders, 22 Feb 1948; Ehrlich, Max; 29 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 326 The Man Who Was Death, 29 Feb 1948; Bester, Alfred; 28 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 327 The Beast of Darrow House, 7 Mar 1948; Barry, Peter; 34 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 328 Stake Out, 14 Mar 1948; Kane, Frank; 31 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 329 Death Coils to Strike, 21 Mar 1948; Baumgartner, Herb; 28 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 330 Death and the Easter Bonnet, 28 Mar 1948; Barry, Peter; 34 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 331 The Ghost that Gleams, 4 Apr 1948; Vittes, Louis; 29 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 332 The Mystery of the Fatal Flowers, 11 Apr 1948; Baumgartner, Herb; 30 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 333 The Geni and the Honorable Thieves, 18 Apr 1948; Barry, Peter; 30 pp. (Box 365)
    - no. 334 A Dark Horse Called Death, 25 Apr 1948; Kane, Frank; 29 pp. (Box 366)
    - no. 335 The Legend of the Living Swamp, 2 May 1948; Baumgartner, Herb; 32 pp. (Box 366)
    - no. 336 Reflection of Death, 9 May 1948; Vittes, Louis; 31 pp. (Box 366)
    - no. 337 The Giant of Madras, 16 May 1948; Barry, Peter; 31 pp. (Box 366)
    - no. 338 Flight Through Darkness, 23 May 1948; Baumgartner, Herb; 33 pp. (Box 366)
    - no. 339 The Ruby of Karvahl, 30 May 1948; Barry, Peter; 33 pp. (Box 366)
    - no. 340 Murder at Dead Man's Inn, 12 Sep 1948; Barry, Peter; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 341 Revenge Is - Murder!, 19 Sep 1948; Kane, Frank; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 342 Death is a Colored Dream, 26 Sep 1948; Vittes, Louis; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 343 The Phantom Racketeer, 3 Oct 1948; Kane, Frank; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 344 A Mask for Murder, 10 Oct 1948; Adamson, Edward J.; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 345 Dead Man's Ride, 17 Oct 1948; Cramoy, Michael; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 346 The Drum of Obi, 24 Oct 1948; Barry, Peter; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 347 Murder by a Corpse, 31 Oct 1948; Adamson, Edward J.; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 348 Evil in the House, 7 Nov 1948; Kane, Frank; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 349 Death and the Throttler of Havenmoor, 14 Nov 1948; Barry, Peter; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 350 The Uncaged Terror, 21 Nov 1948; Adamson, Edward J.; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 366)
    - no. 351 The Wig Makers of Doom Street, 28 Nov 1948; Kane, Frank; 35 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 352 The Laughing Dead, 5 Dec 1948; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 353 The Head of Doom, 12 Dec 1948; Kane, Frank; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 354 The Lost Dead, 19 Dec 1948; Barry, Peter; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 355 Murder Marked Merry Christmas, 26 Dec 1948; Kane, Frank; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 356 Death and the Crown of Odalph, 2 Jan 1949; Barry, Peter; 35 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 357 The Disciple of Death, 9 Jan 1949; Adamson, Edward; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 358 The Sabbath of the Talons, 16 Jan 1949; Barry, Peter; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 359 Death and the Double Cross, 23 Jan 1949; Kane, Frank; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 360 The House of the Ravens, 30 Jan 1949; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 361 The Half Dead Corpse, 6 Feb 1949; Adamson, Edward J.; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 362 Minotau the Avenger', 13 Feb 1949; Barry, Peter; 35 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 363 The Trail of the Knifer, 20 Feb 1949; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 364 Collectors of Death, 27 Feb 1949; Kane, Frank; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 365 Unto Death Do Us Part, 6 Mar 1949; Adamson, Edward J.; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 367)
    - no. 366 The Ring of Mahlalaylee, 13 Mar 1949; Barry, Peter; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 367 The Big Ace, 20 Mar 1949; Kane, Frank; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 368 The Darkcliff Terror, 27 Mar 1949; Kane, Frank; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 369 Creature of Darkness, 3 Apr 1949; Adamson, Edward J.; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 370 Hear No Evil, 10 Apr 1949; Barnum, Merrit W.; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 371 Death and the Easter Bonnet, 17 Apr 1949; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 372 Partners in Crime, 24 Apr 1949; Kane, Frank; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 373 The Double Slug Killer, 1 May 1949; Barry, Peter; 35 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 374 The Buddha and the Snarling Dog, 8 May 1949; Barry, Peter; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 375 Trial by Fire, 15 May 1949; Adamson, Edward; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 376 Murder Counts Ten, 22 May 1949; Kane, Frank; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 377 Monkey Woman, 29 May 1949; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 378 Preview of Terror, 5 Jun 1949; Kane, Frank; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 379 The Secret of the Hidden Room, 11 Sep 1949; Slon, Sidney; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 368)
    - no. 380 The Big Break, 18 Sep 1949; Kane, Frank; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 381 The Death Peddlers, 25 Sep 1949; Kane, Frank; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 382 Death Tips the Odds, 2 Oct 1949; Adamson, Edward J.; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 383 The Phantom Rider, 9 Oct 1949; Barry, Peter; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 384 The Whispering Killer, 23 Oct 1949; Kane, Frank; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 385 The House of Deadly Dreams, 30 Oct 1949; Bester, Alfred; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 386 The Bloody Alley Incident, 6 Nov 1949; Kane, Frank; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 387 The Three Queens of Death, 13 Nov 1949; Barry, Peter; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 388 Deadline, 20 Nov 1949; Slon, Sidney; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 389 The Man with No Face, 27 Nov 1949; Bester, Alfred; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 390 The Ghost from Chinatree, 4 Dec 1949; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 391 Nightmare of the Ghouls, 11 Dec 1949; Kane, Frank; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 392 The Slipper of Death, 18 Dec 1949; Bester, Alfred; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 393 The Christmas Ghost, 25 Dec 1949; Barry, Peter; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 369)
    - no. 394 Resolution of Death, 1 Jan 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 395 The Monster of Blackmire, 8 Jan 1950; Slon, Sidney; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 396 The Bride of Death, 15 Jan 1950; Barry, Peter; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 397 The Ritual of the Hoof, 22 Jan 1950; Bester, Alfred; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 398 The Girl and the Doomed Tiara, 29 Jan 1950; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 399 Dead Head, 5 Feb 1950; Kane, Frank; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 400 The Bride of the Knotted Cord, 12 Feb 1950; Barry, Peter; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 401 The Man with the Burning Head, 19 Feb 1950; Bester, Alfred; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 402 The Stroke of Doom, 26 Feb 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 403 The Dynamite Dummy, 5 Mar 1950; Bester, Alfred; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 404 The Hound of the Long-Dead Lady, 12 Mar 1950; Barry, Peter; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 405 The Curse of the Great Nirvan, 19 Mar 1950; Slon, Sidney; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 406 The Four Forgotten Hours, 26 Mar 1950; Bester, Alfred; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 407 The Insidious Serpent, 2 Apr 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 370)
    - no. 408 The Case of the Curious Easter, 9 Apr 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 409 The Case of the Hanging Ghost, 16 Apr 1950; Kane, Frank; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 410 Death is Your Destination, 23 Apr 1950; Bester, Alfred; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 411 Night of Terror, 30 Apr 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 412 The Other World of Death, 7 May 1950; Bester, Alfred; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 413 The Guest Named Murder, 14 May 1950; Bester, Alfred; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 414 Murder by Scandal, 21 May 1950; Kane, Frank; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 415 The Man Out of Time, 28 May 1950; Bester, Alfred; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 416 Death and the Duchess, 4 Jun 1950; Kane, Frank; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 371)
    - no. 418 Corpse in a Straw Hat, 18 Jun 1950; Roeburt, John "Master Copy"; 26 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 419 The Lost Mind of Death, 25 Jun 1950; Bester, Alfred; 27 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 421 The Mark of the Shark, 9 Jul 1950; 27 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 422 The Curious Corpse, 16 Jul 1950; Ehrlich, Max; 28 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 423 Date with Death, 23 Jul 1950; Ingram, Gail; 28 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 424 The Big Boss, 30 Jul 1950; Ruscoll, Joseph; 28 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 425 The Trail of Treachery, 6 Aug 1950; McGill, Jerry "Master Copy"; 27 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 426 Death Strikes Out, 13 Aug 1950; Ingram, Gail; "Master Copy" and "Recorded Jul 29, 1950; 26 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 428 Murder on Wheels, 27 Aug 1950; McGill, Jerry; "Master Copy" and "Recorded Jul 29, 1950); 27 pp. (Box 371)
    - no. 429 The Man Who Mailed Murder, 3 Sep 1950; Bester, Alfred; "Master Copy" and "Recorded Jul 22, 1950"; 29 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 430 Ring of Death, 10 Sep 1950; Ingram, Gail; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 431 Death Plays a Repeat, 17 Sep 1950; Bester, Alfred; "2nd Revision"; 28 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 432 Messenger of Death, 24 Sep 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; "Revised"; 29 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 433 The Fix, 1 Oct 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 27 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 435 The Gambler, 15 Oct 1950; Ehrlich, Max; 23 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 436 The Chamber of Death!, 22 Oct 1950; Ehrlich, Max; "Final"; 25 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 437 The Ten Dollar Corpse, 29 Oct 1950; Coles, Stedman; "Final"; 28 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 438 The Gift of Gold, 5 Nov 1950; McGill, Jerry "Final"; 24 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 439 Career in Crime, 12 Nov 1950; Adamson, Edward J. "Final"; 26 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 440 Death is a Double Shadow, 19 Nov 1950; Bester, Alfred "Final"; 25 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 441 Flowers for the Corpse, 26 Nov 1950; Ingram, Gail "Final"; 24 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 442 The Cobra, 3 Dec 1950; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; includes pg. 32 from the Jun 18, 1950 show; 27 pp. (Box 372)
    - no. 443 The Forgotten Corpse, 10 Dec 1950; Ingram, Gail; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 444 The Broker of Treason, 17 Dec 1950; Bester, Alfred; "Revised, Final"; 1 copy marked as #431; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 445 Out by Christmas, 24 Dec 1950; Ingram, Gail; 1 copy marked as #432; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 446 Murder by Midnight, 31 Dec 1950; Ingram, Gail; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #433; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 447 The Treasonous Triple Cross, 7 Jan 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #434 and "Final", the other marked as "Revised"; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 449 Double Death, 21 Jan 1951; Ingram, Gail; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #436; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 450 The Friday Fugue, 28 Jan 1951; Lennox, John; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #437; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 451 Man Trap, 4 Feb 1951; Ingram, Gail; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #438; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 372)
    - no. 452 Cargo of Death, 11 Feb 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #439; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 453 The Land Pirates, 18 Feb 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #440; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 454 The Lisp of Death, 25 Feb 1951; Lennox, John; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #441; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 455 Listed for Death, 4 Mar 1951; Copp, Dewitt; "Revised, Final"; 1 copy marked as #442; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 456 The Unwilling Bridegroom, 11 Mar 1951; Brazier, Burt; 1 copy marked as #443; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 457 The Bartering Bride, 18 Mar 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #444; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 458 The Sound of Poison, 25 Mar 1951; Lennox, John; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #445; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 461 The Thought of Murder, 15 Apr 1951; Ingram, Gail; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #448; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 462 Crime in Cash, 22 Apr 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #449; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 464 Murder by a Hair, 6 May 1951; Ingram, Gail; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #451; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 465 Death is a Quack, 13 May 1951; Lennox, John; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #452; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 466 Trial by Fire, 20 May 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #453; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 467 The Deadly Pawn, 27 May 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #454; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 468 The Red Chain, 3 Jun 1951; Bester, Alfred; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #455; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 469 The Curator of Murder, 10 Jun 1951; Bester, Alfred; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #456; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 470 The Twin-Engine Terror, 17 Jun 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #457); 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 373)
    - no. 471 Terror in the Night, 24 Jun 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #458; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 472 The Loom of Death, 1 Jul 1951; Bester, Alfred; 1 copy marked as #459; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 473 Crime on Wheels, 8 Jul 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #460; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 474 Death on the Diamond, 15 Jul 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #461; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 475 Swamp Creature, 22 Jul 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #462; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 476 Last Will and Testament, 29 Jul 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final" and "Recorded Jun 24, 1951"; 1 copy marked as #463; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 477 The Death of Father Neptune, 5 Aug 1951; Bester, Alfred; "Final" and "Recorded Jul 1, 1951"; 1 copy marked as #464; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 478 Vacation from Murder, 12 Aug 1951; Bester, Alfred; "Final" and "Recorded Jun 19, 1951"; 1 copy marked as #465; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 479 The Ten Thousand Dollar Fish, 19 Aug 1951; Bester, Alfred; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #466; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 480 The Lively Corpse, 26 Aug 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #467; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 481 The Deadly Design, 2 Sep 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #468; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 482 The Absolute Alibi, 9 Sep 1951; Lewis, Jonathan; "Final, Revised"; 1 copy marked as #469; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 483 The Curious Ottoman, 16 Sep 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #470; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 484 Invitation to Murder, 23 Sep 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #471; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 485 Bet with Death, 30 Sep 1951; Ingram, Gail; "Final, Revised"; 1 copy marked as #472; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 486 The Factory of Death, 7 Oct 1951; Bester, Alfred; 1 copy marked as #473; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 374)
    - no. 487 A Mind for Murder, 14 Oct 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #474; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 488 The Deadly Bargain, 21 Oct 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #475; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 489 Revenge by Special Delivery, 28 Oct 1951; Bester, Alfred; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #476; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 490 The Final Curtain, 4 Nov 1951; Roeburt, John; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #477; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 491 Record of Murder, 11 Nov 1951; Ingram, Harry; 1 copy marked as #478); 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 492 The Perilous Portrait, 18 Nov 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #479; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 493 The Sound of Dying, 25 Nov 1951; Bester, Alfred; 1 copy marked as #480; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 494 The Dance of Death, 2 Dec 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; "Revised"; other copy marked as #481; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 495 Material Witness, 9 Dec 1951; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #482; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 496 The Search for the Rose Kiss, 16 Dec 1951; Bester, Alfred; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #483; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 497 The Doll with Yellow Hair, 23 Dec 1951; Ingram, Harry; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #484; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 498 The Eve of Murder, 30 Dec 1951; Roeburt, John; 1 copy marked as #485; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 499 Time to Kill, 6 Jan 1952; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #486; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 500 The Case of the Cardboard Club, 13 Jan 1952; Bester, Alfred; 1 copy marked as #487; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 501 Journey to Danger, 20 Jan 1952; Ingram, Harry; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #488; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 502 Death Rides the Range, 27 Jan 1952; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #489; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 503 The Memory of Murder, 3 Feb 1952; Bester, Alfred; 1 copy marked as #490; 23 pp.; 2 copies (Box 375)
    - no. 504 Motive for Murder, 10 Feb 1952; Ingram, Harry; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #491; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 376)
    - no. 505 Murder by Proxy, 17 Feb 1952; Adamson, Edward J.; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #492; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 376)
    - no. 506 Vacation---- with Death, 24 Feb 1952; Ingram, Harry; 1 copy marked as #493; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 376)
    - no. 507 Murder on Time, 2 Mar 1952; Lewis, Jonathan; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #494; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 376)
    - no. 508 The Curious Mr. Jill, 9 Mar 1952; Bester, Alfred; 1 copy marked as #495; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 376)
    - no. 509 The Fall Girl, 16 Mar 1952; Adamson, Edward J.; 1 copy marked as #496; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 376)
    - no. 510 The Ghoul of Darkmoor Graveyard, 23 Mar 1952; Ehrlich, Max; "Final"; 1 copy marked as #497; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 376)